asipartner.com 2018-12-21

# Privacy Policy

ASI Computer Technologies, Inc. (ASI) is committed to protecting the privacy of our customers, especially those who access and use our ASIPartner.com website as well as any of our ancillary websites including partneraccess.com and actonesolution.com. This Privacy Policy is designed to inform you about the types of information that we gather about you and your organization, how we may use that information, whether we disclose it to anyone, and the choices you have regarding our use of that information.

**Collection and Use of Your Personal Information**  
For all visitors to its websites, ASI collects general data pertaining to each Web site visitor, such as the visitor's IP address, operating system, browser type and version number, and the web pages viewed. This information is aggregated with all other visitor information.

ASI collects personal information, which means information by which specific individuals can be identified, including by name, identification number, mailing address, email address, and other personal characteristics or attributes. ASI will process personal information collected from you fairly and lawfully and will not use such personal information for purposes that are incompatible with the purposes it was requested and received. For example, ASI will use your personal information to process orders; to help us to improve our websites and your online experience; to provide you with information about our products and services; for ordering, customer support, payment, processing and service purposes; to transact business with us; for credit checks, collections and related billing or credit purposes; and as otherwise allowed by law.

In addition to personal information you provide to us for the purpose of ordering products, you may provide financial information to us for the purpose of extending credit to you. This data is only used to evaluate your credit worthiness and is reviewed periodically as long as your account is active. It is shared with financial institutions as a normal course of doing business. Your account status and payment history is also reported to various credit reporting agencies.

**Sharing Your Personal Information**  
ASI may share your personal information within our organization, with any ASI subsidiary worldwide, or with authorized third parties (e.g., business partners, suppliers and financial institutions) as described in this policy. We may also disclose information in response to subpoenas, governmental requests or other legal process or to otherwise protect our legal or contractual obligations. We will not sell or otherwise transfer your personal information to individuals or entities outside of us or one of our authorized partners or resellers without your approval.

**Cookies**  
A cookie is type of identifier sent from a website to your computer system via your web browser to provide tailored features. ASI uses cookies in order to secure and confirm your information when logging into partner access with your private login name and password. We do not use this information for any other purpose than to grant you access to secured specific reseller only website pages.

**E-mail Communications**  
ASI provides resellers with promotional announcement for savings, rebates, events and product launches and these announcements can be stopped at any time by selecting the opt- out feature at the bottom of the e-mail. We do not sell these e-mail lists to any of our business partners for any reason.

**Third Party Service: Contests, Events and Webinars**  
From time to time, ASI will collect personal information for contests, events and webinars. This information may be disclosed to our third-party partners for the limited purpose of awarding prizes and/or developing business opportunities.

**Communication Preferences and Reviewing Your Personal Information**  
You can manage your communication preferences by sending an e-mail to [marketing@asipartner.com](mailto:marketing@asipartner.com)  or sending a letter to the mailing address below. When contacting us please include your name, e-mail address, and the details of your request. For example, if you wish to unsubscribe from a newsletter, include the name of the newsletter. You can also access and update your personal information by sending an e-mail to  [marketing@asipartner.com](mailto:marketing@asipartner.com) or sending a letter to the mailing address below that includes you name, e-mail address, account ID and the purpose of the request.

**Security of Your Personal Information**  
ASI uses a combination of industry standard security measures to protect your personal information from loss and misuse. For example, we use encryption when transmitting payment card information over the Internet.

**Children's Privacy**  
ASI does not normally collect the personal information of children under the age of 13. If we do, we require verifiable parental consent, prior to collection. If we learn that we have collected children's personal information without parental consent, we will delete it from our systems.

**How to Contact Us**  
You can contact ASI by sending an e-mail to [marketing@asipartner.com](mailto:marketing@asipartner.com) or sending a letter to the mailing address listed below. Please include your contact information, name of the ASI web site or service, and a detailed description of your request or privacy concern.

ASI Computer Technologies, Inc.   
ATTN: Marketing Department - Privacy  
48289 Fremont Boulevard  
Fremont, CA 94538 USA

ASI reserves the right to change its practices concerning information gathered from visitors to its websites. If such changes occur, this Privacy Policy will be updated. Visitors should check back periodically to confirm the then-current terms of this Policy. This Privacy Policy is not intended to and does not create any contractual or other legal rights in or on behalf of any party.
